Guide to the George Jean Nathan collection, 1913-1958
Nathan, George Jean collection, 1913-1958
- Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, 18th baron, 1878-1957. 3 letters, 1920, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Dunsany, Beatrice 1 letter, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- D'Usseau, Armand 1 letter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Duthie, Eric 1 letter, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Dystel, Oscar, 1912-. 1 letter, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Eastman, Mabel K. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Eaton, Charles Edward 1 letter, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Eaton, W. P. 2 letters, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Edwards, Charles 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Edwards, Hilton 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Elias, Robert H. 1 letter, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Eliot, Jean 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Elizabethan Club of Yale University 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Ellis, Albert 1 letter, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Emmerich Lecture Bureau, Inc. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Emrick, F. Grayson 1 letter, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Encore 1 letter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Encyclopedia Britannica 22 letters, 1928-1948 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Ervine, St. John Greer, 1883-. 18 letters, 1926-1941 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Esquire 7 letters, 1936-1958, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Evans, Floyd Lee 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- The Evening News 1 letter, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Everett, Millard Spencer, 1897-. 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Everitt, Helen 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Ewen, David, 1907-. 1 letter, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Fadiman, Clifton 1 letter, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Fante, John, 1909-. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Farrell, James T. 1 letter, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- fascination 1 letter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Faversham, William, 1868-1940 1 letter, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Fawcett, James Waldo 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Ferber, Edna, 1887-1968. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Feuchtwanger, Lion, 1884-1958. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Ficke, A. D. 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Fischer, Verlag 1 letter, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Fitzgerald, Francis Scott Keye, 1896-1940. 3 letters, 1933, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Flanagan, Hallie 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Ford, Edwin H. 1 letter, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Forgue, Guy J. 1 letter, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Forrest, Belford 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Fort Worth Lecture Foundation 1 letter, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Fowler, J. Beresford 1 letter, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Frank, Bruno 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 81)
- Frankel, Martin 1 letter, 1928, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 82)
- Freedley, George, 1904-1967. 1 letter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 83)
- Freeman, Beatrice R. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 84)
- The Freeman 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 85)
- French, R. E. H. 1 letter, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 86)
- Frisbee, George 1 letter, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 87)
- Furniture Manufacturers Association 2 letters, 1941, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 88)
- Gallico, Paul William, 1897-. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 89)
- Galsworthy, John, 1867-1933. 2 letters, 1924, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 90)
- Gassner, John Waldhorn, 1903-1967. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 91)
- Geller, Harry A. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 92)
- Geller, James J. 1 letter, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 93)
- George, Charles 1 letter, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 94)
- George, W. L. 3 letters, 1921, 1924, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 95)
- Getts, Clark H., 1893-. 1 letter, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 96)
- Getz, S. 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 97)
- Gibbs, Arthur Hamilton, 1888-1956. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 98)
- Glasgow, Ellen 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 99)
- Goguet-Burty, Professor 1 letter, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 100)
- Goldberg, Isaac, -1938. 1 letter, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 101)
- Goodman, Daniel Carson, 1883-1957. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 102)
- Goodman, Eckert 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 103)
- Goodman, Philip 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 104)
- Gould, Bruce 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 105)
- Graham, John A. 1 letter, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 106)
- Graham, Winifred 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 107)
- Graham-Luján, James 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 108)
- Greenberg Publisher 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 109)
- Greene, Ward, 1892-. 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 110)
- Gruenwald, Alfred, 1886-1951. 1 letter, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 111)
- Guichard Co., A. 1 letter, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 112)
- Haendelman, George, E. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 113)
- Haldeman-Julius, E. 2 letters, 1926, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 114)
- Hammerstein, Oscar, 2nd, 1895-1960. 1 letter, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 115)
- Hammett, Samuel Dashiell, 1894-1961. 1 letter, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 116)
- Harper's Baxaar 1 letter, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 117)
- Harris, Frank, 1854-1931. 3 letters, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 118)
- Harvard Law School Forum 1 letter, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 119)
- Hassenclever, Walter 1 letter, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 120)
- Hatch, Frank Ellsworth 2 letters, 1932, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 121)
- Hayes, Helen, 1900-. 1 letter, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 122)
- Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1881-1954. 1 letter, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 123)
- Hazlitt, Henry 4 letters, 1932, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 124)
- Hecht, Ben, 1894-1964. 2 letters, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 125)
- Hegeman, William B. 1 letter, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 126)
- Hellinger, Mark, 1903-1947. 1 letter, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 127)
- Henderson, Archibald, 1877-. 2 letters, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 128)
- Henderson, Florence 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 129)
- Henderson, Frances 1 letter, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 130)
- Henderson, Ray 1 letter, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 131)
- Henshall, George 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 132)
- Herbert, F. Hugh 1 letter, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 133)
- Hergesheimer, Joseph, 1880-1994. 4 letters, 1923, 1924, 1928, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 134)
- Huebach, Ben W., -1964 2 letters, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 135)
- Hewitt, Stanley E. 1 letter, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 136)
- Hildebrand, Howard D. 1 letter, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 137)
- Hill and Wang, Inc. 1 letter, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 138)
- Hinchett, Howard S. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 139)
- Hitchcock, Curtice, 1892-1946. 2 letters, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 140)
- Hobson, Harold, 1904-. 1 letter, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 141)
- Holbrook, Stewart H., 1893-1964. 3 letters, 1928, 1945, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 142)
- Hopkins, Ernest Martin, 1877-1964. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 143)
- Hoptner, Jacob B. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 144)
- Hornblow, A. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 145)
- Horwitz, H. H. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 146)
- Howe, E. W. 2 letters, 1925, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 147)
- Hoyt, Howard E. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 148)
- Hudson, Victor Stuart 1 letter, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 149)
- Huges Massie & Co. 1 letter, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 150)
- Huhner, Dr. Max 1 letter, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 151)
- Huie, William Bradford, 1910-. 1 letter, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 152)
- Humphreys, Cecil 1 letter, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 153)
- Hunecker, James Gibbons, 1860-1921. 4 letters, 1916-1921 (Box 10, Folder 154)
- Hurok, Sol, 1888--. 2 letters, 1926, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 155)
- Hussey, L. M. 6 letters, 1921-1932 (Box 10, Folder 156)
- Hyde, J. Clarence 1 letter, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 157)
- International Magazine Company 2 letters, 1918, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 158)
- Irwin, William Henry, 1873-1948. 1 letter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 159)
- Isaacson, Charles David, 1891-1936. 2 letters, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 160)
- Ish-Kishor, Sulamith 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 161)
- Jacobs, Sidney R. 2 letters, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 162)
- Jameson, Storm[?] 2 letters, 1932, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 163)
- Janvier, Meredith 2 letters, 1930, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 164)
- Jastrow, Joseph, 1863-1944. 2 letters, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 165)
- Jensen, A. C. 1 letter, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 166)
- Jerome, Helen 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 167)
- Johns, Orrick 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 168)
- Johnson, Munnally 1 letter, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 169)
- Jones, Llewellyn 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 170)
- Jones, Warren W. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 171)
- Jones & Green 2 letters, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 172)
- Journal American, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 173)
- Judge Publishing Company, Inc. 5 letters, 1921-1928 (Box 10, Folder 174)
- Kappa Sigma Fraternity 1 letter, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 175)
- Karlweis, Ninon Tallon 2 letters, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 176)
- Kearney, Patrick 2 letters, 1924, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 177)
- Keelan, Harry S. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 178)
- Keithley, Elda U. 1 letter, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 179)
- Kellner, L. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 180)
- Kemler, Edgar, -1960. 6 letters, 1948, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 181)
- Kemp, Harry Hibbard, 1883-. 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 182)
- Kephart, A. P. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 183)
- Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 184)
- [Kerr?], Jean 1 letter, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 185)
- King, Mrs. C. I. 1 letter, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 186)
- King, Helen E. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 187)
- King Features Syndicate 12 letters, 1936-1956 (Box 10, Folder 188)
- Kirkley, Donald 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 189)
- Klaw, Marc, 1859-1936. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 190)
- Kleban, Sylvia 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 191)
- Knickerbocker Publishing Company 1 letter, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 192)
- Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. 10 letters, 1932-1941 (Box 10, Folder 193)
- Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. 21 letters, 1944-1949 (Box 10, Folder 194)
- Knopf, Alfred A., Inc. 25 letters, 1951-1981 (Box 10, Folder 195)
- Kollmar, Richard 1 letter, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 196)
- Koshland, William A. 1 letter, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 197)
- Kozlenko, William, 1908-. 7 letters, 1928-1929, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 198)
- Kroll, Pearl 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 199)
- Krutch, Joseph Wood 3 letters, 192,819,321,933 (Box 10, Folder 200)
- Kutty, V. Gopalan 1 letter, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 201)
- Ladies' Home Journal 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 202)
- Lagner, Lawrence, 1890-. 1 letter, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 203)
- Lancaster, Nathaniel, Jr., 1900-. 1 letter, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 204)
- Lardner, Ring W., 1885-1933. 2 letters, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 205)
- Laurel Lamp Manufacturing Co. 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 206)
- Laurence, Dan H. 1 letter, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 207)
- Lautenbach, Dr. Louis J. 2 letters, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 208)
- Laver, James 2 letters, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 209)
- Lawler, Jack 1 letter, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 210)
- Layton, Frank G. 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 211)
- Leary, P. Q. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 212)
- Le Clercq, Jacques 2 letters, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 213)
- Lee, Gypsy Rose 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 214)
- Leif, Earl H. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 215)
- Leigh, W. Colston, 1901-. 2 letters, 1929, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 216)
- Lemon, G. W. 1 letter, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 217)
- Lengel, William C. 1 letter, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 218)
- Lenox Hill Players, Inc. 1 letter, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 219)
- Levin, Ethel 1 letter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 220)
- Lewis, Alfred Henry, -1914. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 221)
- Lewis, Oscar, 1893-. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 222)
- Lewis, Wilmarth Sheldon, 1895-. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 223)
- Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951. 23 letters, 1926-1941, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 224)
- Lewisohn, Ludwig 3 letters, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 225)
- Liberty 1 letter, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 226)
- LIFE 2 letters, 1921, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 227)
- Limanag, Fely T. 2 letters, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 228)
- Limited Edtions Club 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 229)
- Lind, Dr. John E. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 230)
- Lindsey, Ben B 1 letter, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 231)
- Linne, Martha Boyd 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 232)
- Littell, Robert, 1896-. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 233)
- Littlewood, S. R. 1 letter, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 234)
- Logan, Harlan de Baun, 1904-. 1 letter, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 235)
- Long, Ray, 1878-1935. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 236)
- Lonsdale, Frederick, 1881-1954 2 letters, 1949, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 237)
- Lucas, Vernon A. 1 letter, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 238)
- Lundalle, R. 3 letters, Ca. 1920, 1922, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 239)
- Lyons, Eugene, 1898-. 2 letters, 1949, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 240)
- M.P.T. League for Better Pictures 1 letter, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 241)
- Macaulay, Rose 3 letters, 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 242)
- McBride, Robert M. & Company 1 letter, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 243)
- McCarty, Mary 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 244)
- McDermott, William F., 1891-. 2 letters, 1937, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 245)
- MacDonald, Douglas W. 1 letter, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 246)
- MacDonald, Duncan Elliot, 1919-. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 247)
- McElroy, William 2 letters, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 248)
- McFee, William 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 249)
- McGovern, John Terrence, 1876-. 1 letter, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 250)
- Machamer, Jefferson 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 251)
- McIntyre, Alfred Robert, 1886-1948. 1 letter, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 252)
- McIntyre, Oscar Odd, 1884-1938. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 253)
- Mack, Willard 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 254)
- McKinney, Marsh & Cushing 1 letter, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 255)
- McManus, Father 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 256)
- McMurphy 1 letter, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 257)
- McWilliams, Carey, 1905-. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 258)
- Macy, John 1 letter, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 259)
- Madden, Richard J. 5 letters, 1937, 1940, 1941, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 260)
- Maggini, Donald 1 letter, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 261)
- Malott, Deane Waldo, 1898-. 1 letter, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 262)
- Manchester, William B. 8 letters, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 263)
- Mann, Thomas 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 264)
- Mantle, Burns, 1873-1948. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 265)
- Maril, Dr. Konrad 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 266)
- Marmor, Matthew 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 267)
- Marrow, Peter 1 letter, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 268)
- Marshall, Armina 1 letter, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 269)
- Massaguer, Conrad W. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 270)
- Mathews, Jerry A. 1 letter, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 271)
- Matson and Duggan 1 letter, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 272)
- Mayo, Margaret 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 273)
- Mearns, David Chambers, 1899-. 2 letters, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 274)
- Mencken, August 8 letters, 1950, 1952, 1956, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 275)
- Mencken, Henry Louis, 1880-1956. 4 items, 1920, 1943, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 276)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 24 letters, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 277)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 24 letters, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 278)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 24 letters, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 279)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 20 letters, 1923-1930 (Box 10, Folder 280)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 31 letters, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 281)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 35 letters, 1935-1941 (Box 10, Folder 282)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 34 letters, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 283)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 27 letters, 1943 (January-April) (Box 10, Folder 284)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 35 letters, 1943 (May-December) (Box 10, Folder 285)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 30 letters, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 286)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 47 letters, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 287)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 29 letters, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 288)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 14 letters, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 289)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 29 letters, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 290)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 10 letters, 1949-1955 (Box 10, Folder 291)
- Meyer, Torben 1 letter, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 292)
- Meyers, Alfred Louis 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 293)
- Middleman, Adele Dorothea 2 letters, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 294)
- Millar, F. W. & Co. Ltd. 1 letter, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 295)
- Miller, Gilbert Heron, 1884-. 2 letters, 1932, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 296)
- Miller, Henry John, 1860-1926. 1 letter, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 297)
- MiRamora, Elena 1 letter, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 298)
- Mizener, Arthur 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 299)
- Modern Thinker 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 300)
- Moe, Henry Allen, 1894-. 1 letter, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 301)
- Mohrenwitx, Dr. L. 2 letters, 1932, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 302)
- Mok, Michel 1 letter, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 303)
- Monfried, Walter 1 letter, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 304)
- Moore, Grace, 1901-1947 1 letter, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 305)
- Morand, Paul 2 letters, 1933, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 306)
- Morgan, Charles, 1894-. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 307)
- Morris, Gouverneur, 1876-1953 8 letters, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 308)
- Morrison, Hugh 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 309)
- Morse, Helen Kelton 1 letter, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 310)
- Muir, Malcolm 1 letter, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 311)
- Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 312)
- Mundey, Meg 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 313)
- Munson, John J. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 314)
- Murray, J. McCombie 1 letter, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 315)
- Mussolini, Benito, 1883-1945. [from Royal Italian Embassy] 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 316)
- Musters, Georgina 1 letter, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 317)
- Myerberg, Michael 1 letter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 318)
- Nathan, Julie Haydon, 1910-. 7 letters, 1955, 1956, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 319)
- Nevinson, Henry W. 2 letters, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 320)
- New English Weekly 1 letter, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 321)
- New Freeman 1 letter, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 322)
- New York Evening Graphic 1 letter, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 323)
- New York Herald Tribune 1 letter, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 324)
- New Yorker 2 letters, 1937, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 325)
- Newton, Byron Rufus, 1861-1938 1 letter, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 326)
- Nichols, Dudley 1 letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 327)
- Nichols, William Ichabod, 1905-. 1 letter, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 328)
- North American Newspaper Alliance, Inc. 1 letter, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 329)
- O'Brien, Mary B. 1 letter, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- O'Brien, Eileen 3 letter, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- O' Casey, Sean, 1880-1964 30 letters, 1932-1935 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- O' Casey, Sean 33 letters, 1936-1940 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- O'Casey, Sean 26 letters, 1941-1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- O' Casey, Sean 31 letters, 1947-1950 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- O' Casey, Sean 31 letters, 1951-1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- O'Casey, Sean 26 letters, 1955-1958, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Oelrichs, Hermann 1 letter, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- O'Fahey, Martin J. 1 letter, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- O'Malley, Ira J. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 11)
- O'Neill, Carlotta 20 letters, 1935-1952 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone, 1888-1953 25 letters, 1919-1927 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone 21 letters, 1928-1931 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone 28 letters, 1932-1936 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone 23 letters, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone 23 letters, 1941-1949 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone 11 letters, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Orton, Vrest Teachout 1 letter, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- O'Sullivan, Vincent 1 letter, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Otvos, A. Dorian 1 letter, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Oursler, Charles Fulton, 1893-. 2 letters, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- P.E.N. 1 letter, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Packard, Irving H. 1 letter, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Paine, Albert Bigelow, 1861-1937. 1 letter, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Parade Publication Inc. 2 letters, 19,421,943 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Parmount Pictures Inc. 2 letters, 1939, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Parrish, Ann 1 letter, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Parshley, Howard M. 1 letter, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Patten, Gilbert, 1866-1945. 1 letter, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Patterson, F. T. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Paulsen II, Henry C. 1 letter, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Paulson, Arvid 4 letters, 1946, 1952, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Paynter, E. W. 1 letter, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Pearson, Drew, 1897-. 3 letters, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Pendray, G. Edward, 1901-. 1 letter, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Perkins, Troy L. 2 letters, 1934, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Perkins-Goodwin Co. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Pijoan, Joseph 1 letter, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Pinson[?], Arthur 1 letter, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Pinthus, Dr. Kurt 1 letter, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Piscadera Bay Club 1 letter, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Pither[?], Patricia 1 letter, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Pitt Theatre Company 1 letter, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Pittsburgh Drama League 1 letter, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Plain Talk 1 letter, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 46)
- The Players Co. 1 letter, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Pohl, Frederick J. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Pond, James Burton 2 letters, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Pope, Quentin 1 letter, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Porth, Walter H. 1 letter, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Postle, Stuart A., Jr. 1 letter, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Pound, Reginald 2 letters, 1937, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Powers, Robert 1 letter, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Powers, T. J. 1 letter, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Powys, Llewelyn, 1884-1939. 2 letters, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Pride, Leo B. 1 letter, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Priestley, J. B. 3 letters, 1932, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Principals' Club of Hartford 1 letter, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- [Pringle?], Aileen 1 letter, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- PUCK 1 letter, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Purdy, James 1 letter, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Querschnitt, Der 1 letter, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- R.K.O. Radio Pictures Inc. 2 letters, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Raddock, Charles 1 letter, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Rafferty, K. G. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Rascoe, Burton, 1892-. 3 letters, 1927, 1932, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Ratcliffe, S. K. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Ray, Rene 1 letter, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Recht, Charles 1 letter, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Redbook 1 letter, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Reinhardt, Max, 1873-1943. 1 letter, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Reynal, Eugene, 1902-. 1 letter, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Rhodes, June Hamilton 1 letter, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Rice, Elmer, 1892-. 1 letter, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Rinehart & Company 1 letter, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Rivas, Humberto 1 letter, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Robb, Walter 1 letter, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Roberts, Kingsley, 1893-1947. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Robinson, Jane R. 1 letter, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Rocky Mountain News 1 letter, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Rogers, O. V. T. 1 letter, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 82)
- Rose, Enid 1 letter, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 83)
- Rose, Sidney 1 letter, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 84)
- Ross, Harold Wallace 2 letters, 1949, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 85)
- Rowe, Leonard 1 letter, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- Royce Publishers 1 letter, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Rubinstein, Marion 1 letter, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 88)
- Ruby, Harry, 1895-. 1 letter, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- Russell, Virginia 1 letter, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- Saint, W. Daniel 1 letter, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 91)
- St. John, Betta 1 letter, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 92)
- Sandburg, Carl, 1878-. 9 letters, 1949-1957, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 93)
- Santayana, George, 1863-1952. 1 letter, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- Saroyan, William, 1908-1981. 24 letters, 1928-1940 (Box 11, Folder 95)
- Saroyan, William 23 letters, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 96)
- Saroyan, William 12 letters, 1943-1957, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 97)
- Saturday Review 2 letters, 1936, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 98)
- Schuster, Max Lincoln, 1897-. 2 letters, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 99)
- Schuyler, George S., 1895-. 1 letter, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 100)
- Scott, Evelyn 1 letter, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 101)
- Seaman, Herbert W. 2 letters, 1931, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 102)
- Selwyn, Edgar 2 letters, 1941, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 103)
- Serwer, Harry 2 letters, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 104)
- Shanaf, S. 1 letter, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 105)
- Shaw, George Bernard, 1856-1950. 1 letter and 1 photograph, 1944, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 106)